luckyscent.com 2019-09-06

# Privacy and Security | Luckyscent

Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. We at Luckyscent want to make your experience online satisfying and safe. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it. 

If you have opted-in to receive updates from luckyscent.com, we may use your e-mail address as a means to contact you, our customer, regarding updates to the luckyscent.com site, new product offerings, and/or ways in which we can improve your future shopping experiences at luckyscent.com. You can always decide that you want to stop receiving any of these updates by opting out of our database by going to our unsubscribe page.

## Types of information that we collect:

We may collect personally identifiable information about you through our Service when you register for an account, such as your email address. If you choose to purchase a product from us, we or our third-party payment processors will collect your payment information also. When you use our Service or if you visit such websites, your browser may send us certain information about you as described below. We send promotional emails. If you no longer wish to receive these emails, you may opt out of them by canceling your account. We do not share or sell any of our customers' personal information with third parties.  

## Cookies

Luckyscent.com uses "cookies" to allow our customers to add items to their Shopping Cart, to travel to other pages within the site, and then to return to find their basket contents intact. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will most likely receive a warning message.

Our servers track the type of web browser you are using, the page to which you link from, and which pages of our website are most popular. We collect this information to better understand what products and services are of interest to luckyscent.com visitors.

## Product Reviews

Product reviews submitted by Luckyscent account holders may be used by Luckyscent to further promote the products for which the reviews were posted or the service provided by Luckyscent. 

## Third Party Cookies: 

Our partners, affiliates, and service providers use cookies to: (a) monitor the effectiveness of our Service and the offerings of our partners; (b) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns; (c) diagnose or fix technology problems; (d) and allow our business partners to deliver advertisements to you as described below. These include the use of cookies by our partners, affiliates and service providers are not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access and control over the use of these cookies on our site. Our third party providers colllect pseudonymous data that allows them to single out individual behavior without directly identifying the individuals saving any personal information. Those providers are currently Criteo, Adroll, Google Analytics and Adwords, Facebook, and AddThis. 

You can stop Cookies from being downloaded to your device from the luckyscent.com services at any time by selecting the appropriate settings in your browser. Most browsers will tell you how to change your browser settings to notify you when a Cookie is being set or updated, or to restrict or block certain types or all Cookies. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information or by visiting�[www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). 

For more information on managing Analytics Cookies, please use the following links:

## Security:

At luckyscent.com, security issues are of the utmost importance. Luckyscent.com uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology by COMODO to encrypt all of your personal information. SSL is part of the strong security measures we use to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of your information. If you are using the lastest version of your browser, all sales transactions on luckyscent.com will be fully encrypted and secure. If you use a relay or proxy you can make sure that your connection is secure by checking your browser's lock indicator. 

## Ads:

We use Remarketing with Google Analytics, Criteo, Oracle and Facebook to advertise online. In connection with this advertising, we, along with third-party business partners, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) to allow our third-party business partners, including Google, ad servers, and ad networks, to serve you advertisements ("ads") based on your prior visits to our Service. These ads are delivered to you on third-party websites and services across the Internet. These third-party business partners use technology to send, directly to your browser or mobile device, the ads and ad links that appear on third-party sites, and will automatically receive your IP address when they do so. Along with cookies, they may also use other technologies (such as JavaScript, device identifiers, location data, see above) to compile information about your browser's or device's visits and usage patterns on the Service, and to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to optimize and personalize the advertising content. Luckyscent does not sell, rent, or share the information we collect directly from you or about you from third parties with these third-party business partners for such parties' own marketing purposes. You may opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page or you may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the Google Analytics opt-out page. Google has additional information available about their Remarketing Privacy Guidelines, Policies, and Restrictions. The Luckyscent Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, third-party ad servers and ad networks. Please contact or consult the respective privacy policies of such ad servers or ad networks for more information.
